[{"id": 2585, "question": "According to the dictionary definition of 'create',ordinary people are creative every day. To create means to bring into being,to cause to exist something each of us does daily. We are creative whenever we look at or think about something in a new way. First,this includes an awareness of our surroundings. It means using all of our senses to become aware of our world. This may be as simple as being aware of color1 and texture ,as well as taste, when we plan a meal. Above all,it is the ability to notice things that others might miss. A second part of creativity is an ability to see relationships among things. If we believe the expression,there is nothing new under the sun,the creativity is remaking or recombining the old in new ways. For example,we might do this by finding a more effective w...\n\nQ: There is nothing new under the sun really implies that   _  .", "options": ["a new thing can only be created at the basis of earliest things", "a new thing is only a tale", "we can seldom create new things", "we can hardly see really new things in the world"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 463, "question": "Flying Ever since I was old enough to dream,I have imagined myself soaring with the eagles.My love of flying has shaped the way I live and the person I have become.Two years ago,that passion rocketed to new heights when I had the opportunity to visit Embry Riddle Aeronautical University in Arizona.For a whole week I lived in a college dorm,roomed with a total stranger and---best of all---I flew! My group took part in activities ranging from learning about the history of aviation to flying in state-of-the-art pilot training simulators .At least once a day,I devoted myself to learning one of the world's best training aircrafts,the Cessna 182.Not only did I receive thorough ground instruction,but I also got to fly.In total,I flew five hours to receive my private pilot's license. In that one j...\n\nQ: According to the author,   makes people unique.", "options": ["flying like an eagle", "trying something special", "having their own dreams", "learning unusual techniques"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2694, "question": "Every day we meet people in a number of business and social situations. And the way we meet and greet them creates an impression. It's important to do so in a proper way, no matter whether you are introducing yourself to someone, or introducing two people. To keep you aware of this, we have gathered tips on how to make a proper introduction. *Always stand when making an introduction. When you are seated and someone comes up to greet you, make the effort to stand up. By doing this, you show respect for yourself and for the other person. *Always keep eye contact while making an introduction. Many people are not aware of the value of this simple action. When you make eye contact, you are giving a confident image. *Always introduce a person of lesser authority to one of greater authority. The ...\n\nQ: What should you do when you introduce a new worker to your boss?", "options": ["You should not give your boss' name.", "You should give the new worker's name first.", "You needn't give your boss' name", "You should give your boss' name first"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2201, "question": "'Well,' began Enfield, 'I was coming home about three o'clock on a black winter morning, when suddenly I saw two people. The first was a short man who was walking along the street, and the second was a little girl who was running as fast as she could. Well, the two bumped into each other and the child fell down. Then a terrible thing happened. The man calmly walked all over the child's body with his heavy boots, and left her screaming on the ground. It was an inhuman thing to do. I ran after the man, caught him and fetched him back. There was already a small crowd around the screaming child. The man was perfectly cool, but he gave me a very evil look, which made me feel sick in my stomach. The child's family then arrived, and also a doctor. The child had been sent to fetch the doctor for a...\n\nQ: Which of the following is true according to the passage above?", "options": ["The little girl was frightened as well as seriously hurt.", "The doctor did not trust the short man and disliked him.", "The short man willingly paid the little girl's family a hundred pounds.", "The doctor was present at the spot to see what was wrong with the little girl."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 42, "question": "One of the traditions which is now a necessary part of Christmas is a that of Father Christmas, or Santa Claus. According to the modern legend, he is a magical figure who visits all the children of the world during the night before Christmas Day, leaving presents which they find the next morning. He flies through the night sky in a sledge pulled by reindeer, and enters houses by climbing down chimneys. This strange legend is based on the life of a man called Nicholas, but in fact we know very little about him. Historians think he was a Christian bishop in Turkey in about 285--350 A.D. One of the stories about him is that he helped three poor girls. No one would marry them because they were so poor. To provide them with money for their weddings, Nicholas secretly dropped some gold coins dow...\n\nQ: The writer mentions details such as Father Christmas's sledge, the reindeer and the way he climbs down chimneys because he/she  _", "options": ["wants to make it clear that these things are impossible", "is describing the history of St Nicholas", "wants everyone to believe that Father Christmas is real", "is explaining the modern legend of Father Christmas"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 578, "question": "Read the following reviews for movies that are showing at the moment. And then answer questions. Happiness(Romance) Happinesstells the story of two people (Lisa Turbot and Danny Roy) who work for different advertising companies. They talk on the phone all the time and don't like each other. But then they _ by e-mail and fall in love. This movie will be very popular with teenagers and people who like romances. It also has beautiful music. I Scream(Thriller) InI Scream, Paul (Colin Jacks) is a young man who joins a thriller club. Each of the members tries to frighten the others. Paul is told to stay in an old house for the night. Everyone who has tried to stay in the house before has died. This movie is very frightening but also quite silly. It doesn't make sense for Paul to stay in the hous...\n\nQ: Which of the four movies is the least popular with people?", "options": ["The 1st one.", "The 2nd one.", "The 3rd one.", "The 4th one."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2523, "question": "\"A good parent\" can be a confusing phrase. It is almost impossible for one person to be \"a good parent\" at all stages of a child's life. Some parents are at their best before their children begin to speak. Others are most successful before their children enter elementary school. Still others make their finest contribution to older children or teenagers. Every parent can understand one stage of a child's development better than another. It is hard for a person to possess superior capacities throughout the entire period of a child's growth. A mother might be \"a good parent\" from her baby's birth until it is three; that is the period when it needs her protection and loving care. Then the start of her child's independence might upset and alarm her, and she might then become less helpful for a ...\n\nQ: Parents would feel guilty if   _  .", "options": ["their children can't accept their own limitations of talent", "they realize their weaknesses in raising children", "their grandfathers and uncles and aunts don't live with them", "they don't know their limitations in raising children"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2062, "question": "It was time for a school holiday and I was at home. My family's house was located in an area by the sea. I just sat down in front of the television. Suddenly I heard a loud noise and then the first shock started to hit. My mom and I ran to the front door. We got out and we were standing in the street holding on to each other to stand up. The ground was covered with snow. I could remember watching black cracks in the earth snaking their way along the ground. A tree in our back yard was actually cut in half. As suddenly as the earthquake started, it was over. Dead silence. Then a light snow began to fall. All the power was off--no radio, no TV and no communication with the outside world. We found out later that the ground area was lowered an average of 35 feet. My dad succeeded in getting ho...\n\nQ: After the earthquake, the writer's father   _  .", "options": ["opened up his own company", "lived with his family and did a better job", "helped neighbors build their houses", "became a famous person in their town"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 657, "question": "Want to know the dynamic pulse of China's economy? Get a glance of the most important business activities taking place here every day through Business Daily Update, a service offered by China Daily information via the World Wide Web. Placed under 10 categories, over 25 news items appear each day with the top three events highlighted all in English.Business Daily Update is just a few mouse clicks away. Subscribe to BDU for an annual fee of US $240.Email and fax services are also Available upon request. For more information, please contact Business Daily Update: Tel: (010)64941107, (010) 64924488 ext.2000; Fax: +86-10-64941125 Email: bdu@chinadaily.com.cn;URL:http://www.chinadaily.com.cn/bdu...\n\nQ: If you get into BDU, you can   _  .", "options": ["get the information of the latest business activities taking place in China", "get the most important business information in the world", "know more than what you expect in China", "get all the information in China Daily"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 2268, "question": "People appear to be born to calculate. The numerical skills of children develop so early that it is easy to imagine an internal clock of mathematical maturity guiding their growth. Not long after learning to walk and talk, they can set the table with impressive accuracy--one plate, one knife, one spoon, one fork for each of the five chairs. Soon they are capable of noting that they have placed five knives, spoons and forks on the table, and a bit later, that this amounts to fifteen pieces of silverware. Having thus mastered addition, some people expect that if a child were on a desert island at birth and brought back seven years later, he or she could enter a second-grade mathematics class without any serious problems of intellectual adjustment. Of course, the truth is not so simple. This ...\n\nQ: Which of the following statements would the author most likely be against?", "options": ["Children learn mathematics naturally and easily.", "Children learn to add before they learn to subtract.", "Most people follow the same pattern of mathematical development.", "Mathematical development is unnoticeable and gradual."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3190, "question": "An American research company shows that $248.7 billion online sales are expected by 2014. It seems as if we can't get enough of spending money through countless online clicks today. Following are some of the incredible things that you can buy online! 1) Parents 51-year-old Michael Amatrudo from Connecticut put a posting on Craig list in 2009 to sell his elderly parents, asking for $155 in return. 2) Chewing Gum Bidding for Britney Spears' chewing gum reached $14,000 in 2004. The pop star's half-eaten sandwich also went for over $500. 3) Kidney Stone Star Trek actor William Shatner sold his kidney stone for $20,000 when he put it up for sale online to see how much a piece of him was worth. He ended up giving the money to charity. 4) An Imaginary Friend This imaginary guy went (or might stil...\n\nQ: Which is probably sold at the highest price according to the passage?", "options": ["Chewing Gum.", "Kidney Stone.", "An Imaginary Friend.", "A Rock That Looks Like Meat."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 621, "question": "Is there anything more important than health?I don't think so.You can't be good at your studies or work when you are ill. If you have a headache,or a bad cough,if you run a high temperature and have a bad cold,I think you should go to the doctor. The doctor will examine your throat,feel your pulse,take your temperature,sound your heart and lungs.After that he will advise some treatment,or some medicine.The only thing you have to do is to follow his advice. Speaking of doctor's advice,I can't help telling you a funny story. An old man came to see the doctor.The man was very ill.He told the doctor about his weakness,memory loss and serious problems with his heart and lungs.The doctor examined him and said there was no medicine for his disease. He told his patient to go to a quiet place for a...\n\nQ: The writer thinks that   _  .", "options": ["health is more important than wealth", "work is as important as studies", "medicine is more important than pleasure", "nothing is more important than money"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 1290, "question": "Surtsey was born in 1963. Scientists saw the birth of this island.It began at 7:30 am . on 14th November . A fishing boat was near Iceland.The boat moved under the captain's feet . He noticed a strange smell.He saw some black smoke .A volcano was breaking out . Red hot rocks,fire and smoke were rushing up from the bottom of the sea . The island grew quickly.It was 10 metres high the next day and 60 metres high on 18th November. Scientists flew there to watch.It was exciting.Smoke and fire were still rushing up. Pieces of red hot rock were flying into the air and falling into the sea. The sea was boiling and there was a strange light in the sky. Surtsey grew and grew. Then it stopped in June 1967. It was 175 metres high and 2 kilometres 1ong.And life was already coming to Surtsey. Plants gr...\n\nQ: The best title of the text is  _  .", "options": ["New Discovery .", "The Birth of An Island.", "A Captain and An Island .", "How Does A Volcano Break Out."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 181, "question": "School education is very important and useful. Yet no one can learn everything from school. A teacher, no matter how much he knows, he can not teach his students everything they want to know. The teacher's job is to show his students how to learn. He teaches them how to read and how to think. So much more is to be learned outside school by the students themselves. It is always more important to know how to study by oneself than to learn some facts or a formula by heart. It is actually quite easy to learn a certain fact in history or a formula in mathematics. But it is very difficult to use a formula in working out a maths problem. Great scientist, such as Einstein, Newton and Galileo, didn't get everything from school. But they were all so successful and invented so many things for men. Th...\n\nQ: What's the good advice the writer gives us?", "options": ["We can learn better without teachers", "We should do more asking and thinking while studying", "We should pay enough attention to classroom", "Book knowledge is little use"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1951, "question": "\"It was cool,because I got a chance to be in a studio and see how a record is made,\"says 14-year-old Javon Martin,who joined the music clubhouse 3 years ago.\"It has impacted my life in a big way. People are actually starting to see me as an artist.\"Ten-year-old Akheylah Hunter didn't play an instrument when she became a club member last year. Now,she plays piano and sings with the band. What she likes best,she says,is performing.\"We performed in different places,\"she says.\"We go on trips and it is fun.\" Since the Music Clubhouse opened three years ago,it's served almost 500 kids.Aggeler says performing in front of different audiences helps the young musicians build self-esteem.Coming to the club to prepare for those performances helps them learn how to deal with their personal problems and...\n\nQ: What does the writer intend the passage to be?", "options": ["An advertisement for a club.", "A promotion of some non-profit groups.", "An introduction of a music club for children.", "A try to call for attention on children's needs."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 1273, "question": "Spring is the time to go out and enjoy the weather and scenery.Here are some events to attend in March of 2012 in Oregon! Oregon Country Fair(OCF), 9 am to 7 pm on March 8 - 10 OCF first started in 1969, and it's blossomed into an outstanding example of what a non - profit should be. OCF is an event of shopping & atmosphere, and food ranging from Indian & Afghani cuisine to Italian & France cuisine.Wonderful craft & music never stop.From the time you get there until the time you leave, everyone has a smile on their faces, and they wave and say hello.For tickets, go and visit www.Oregoncountryfair.org. 30thAnnual Seaside Beach Volleyball Tournament, 8 am to 6 pm on March 12 - 14 The Annual Seaside Beach Volleyball Tournament is an amateur tournament that draws amateur volleyball players to ...\n\nQ: Locals of the Oregon coast are afraid of the relay because   _  .", "options": ["the relay will last a long period", "they have to offer food and water", "the weather is bad during the relay", "too many people will go there"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2059, "question": "The vast jungles of the Amazon rainforest are home to tribes mostly isolated from the outside world,whose way of life,largely unchanged for hundreds of years,is now increasingly threatened by modern civilization. Now, scientists discover they can monitor these\"uncontacted tribes\"using satellites,which would allow inexpensive and safe tracking of these tribes in order to protect them from outside threats. In order to help conserve these uncontacted Indians,researchers need accurate estimates of their populations.One way to collect this data involves flying over their villages,but such overflights are both expensive and could fill these native peoples with fear.Another strategy involves meeting individuals on the ground,but among other risks,scientists could accidentally spread disease to me...\n\nQ: Scientists don't want to meet the Indians on the ground due to the fear that  _", "options": ["they can't get accurate data", "they will be attacked by the Indians", "they could pass disease to the Indians", "they will catch disease from the Indians"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 3308, "question": "In the 19thcentury, Americans from the eastern states moved out west to settle in the rich new lands along the Pacific Coast. The most difficult part of their trip was crossing \"the Great American Desert\" in the western part of the United States by horse and wagon. The western desert can be very dangerous. There is little water and there are few trees. But the desert also has scenery of great beauty. Tall towers of red and yellow stone rise sharply from the flat, sandy valley floor. The scene has been photographed many times and appears in movies and on TV. In Arizona, man-made dams across the Colorado River have made two large lakes in the middle of the dry desert country. At Lake Powell, the red stone arch of Rainbow Bridge rises high above the blue lake. There are few roads. Many areas ...\n\nQ: In the desert, animals will die  _  .", "options": ["if they move about", "if they can't make holes underground", "if they come out at night", "if they drink much water"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1340, "question": "Once a general manager wanted to test his people, who had come from all over India, about their values of life. He announced that in their folders , there is PVC pouch and in it there is a seed. When they return, they must put the seed in a pot with good soil and look after it very well. He would hold a competition at the next year's seminar and the best plants would be awarded suitably. Everyone did what was told to him. A year passed quickly. And the next year in a big hall, what a great scene! There were hundreds of pots and a great variety of plants-all except one. In this pot was soil, but no plant! The owner of the pot was standing quietly and feeling ashamed of himself. The general manager called him on the stage. He asked him what happened and he told him the truth. He planted the ...\n\nQ: The man in the passage failed to get the plant because  _  .", "options": ["he didn't take good care of his seed", "he wasn't good at planting", "his seed wasn't as good as the other people's", "the seed had been boiled"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1289, "question": "Surtsey was born in 1963. Scientists saw the birth of this island.It began at 7:30 am . on 14th November . A fishing boat was near Iceland.The boat moved under the captain's feet . He noticed a strange smell.He saw some black smoke .A volcano was breaking out . Red hot rocks,fire and smoke were rushing up from the bottom of the sea . The island grew quickly.It was 10 metres high the next day and 60 metres high on 18th November. Scientists flew there to watch.It was exciting.Smoke and fire were still rushing up. Pieces of red hot rock were flying into the air and falling into the sea. The sea was boiling and there was a strange light in the sky. Surtsey grew and grew. Then it stopped in June 1967. It was 175 metres high and 2 kilometres 1ong.And life was already coming to Surtsey. Plants gr...\n\nQ: When did scientists fly there to watch the birth of the island?", "options": ["Before the volcano broke out.", "On 14th November 1963 .", "About four days after the volcano broke out .", "In June 1967."], "answer": 2}, {"id": 2537, "question": "When you sleep somewhere else--like at summer camp or a friend's house--you know you're in for a fun time. It can be exciting to get away from the same old bed in the same old room in the same old house. But fun as this is, for some kids being away from home can be scary and sad. They want to go and have fun with their friends, but once they're there, they start to miss their good old bed, their good old parents, and all that everyday stuff at home. It's called being homesick. Homesick means you're upset, sad, and maybe scared. But don't feel surprised. A lot of people get homesick, even grownups. When you're used to having certain people and things around you, it can be scary when they're gone. When you're dealing with other problems, you will feel homesick, too. Some kids may feel more h...\n\nQ: Kids won't feel homesick when   _  .", "options": ["they are dealing with the problems", "the people and things they get used to are around them", "someone they loved has recently died", "their parents are getting divorced"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2977, "question": "Most Americans receive at least two or three credit card applications in the mail every month.Why have credit cards become so popular? For a merchant, the answer is obvious.By putting charge slips in a bank, the merchant can change credit card sales into cash.In return for processing the merchant's credit card transactions , the bank charges a fee that ranges between 1.5 and 5 percent. The easiest way to establish credit is to open checking and savings accounts at your local bank.Then apply for a gasoline or store credit card.These cards are fairly easy to get because retailers want you to buy their goods and services.The third step, and the most dangerous one, is obtaining a major credit card like Visa, MasterCard, or American Express. It is important to choose a credit card carefully bec...\n\nQ: What is the disadvantage of a credit card?", "options": ["The bank charges annual fees for credit cards.", "The interest rate for credit cards is rather high.", "Credit cards cause argument among holders and banks.", "Credit cards tend to lead card holder into debt"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 18, "question": "A girl with blue eyes is a blue-eyed girl. A man with long legs is a long-legged man. A woman with white hair is a white-haired woman. Children who have good looks are good-looking children. What do you do when you want to buy clothes? You go to a shop. If you can find clothes that are the right size for you, and if they are ready to wear, you will probably buy them. They are called ready-made clothes. If you can not find clothes that are the right size, you will go to a tailor's shop. A tailor is a man who makes clothes. He will measure you carefully and will then make clothes for you. Such clothes are called tailor-made clothes. What do we call a man who is dressed badly? We call him a badly-dressed man. A woman who is dressed well is called a well-dressed woman. What do you wear when it...\n\nQ: 58. What do you think is the best title for the article?", "options": ["The Forms of Compound Words.", "Compound Words in Everyday Life", "How to Use Compound Words.", "Water-proof Cloth in the Best."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1702, "question": "My mom has eyes in the back of her head. She also taught me from an early age to be suspicious of strange men, especially when they give you presents. One day, a \"nice man\" bearing flowers managed to steal 20 euros from her purse, while she was holding it in her hands. \"He said he was collecting for a church charity so I pulled out a euro,\" she explains, \"He said 'no, no, that's too much' and offered to look in my purse to find a smaller coin. He must have slid out that 20 euro note at the same time. I did not even notice until an hour later. I felt so stupid.\" According to neuroscientists, the key requirement for a successful pickpocket is not having nifty fingers, it's having a working knowledge of the loopholes in our brain. The most important of these loopholes is the fact that our bra...\n\nQ: According to the passage, all of the following are pickpocket strategies except   _  .", "options": ["having nifty fingers", "hanging out \"beware of pickpockets\" sign", "displaying confidence", "moving hand in an arc motion"], "answer": 0}, {"id": 433, "question": "Health insurance can be very expensive. Some working people do not make enough money to pay for it. In the US there is a program called Healthy Families. This program offers people health insurance at a low cost. Families are charged about $7.00 a month for every child, and $10.00 for every adult. It costs much less than any other kind of health insurance. Having health insurance is very important. With this insurance, people can see a doctor when they are sick or hurt. The program is not expensive at all, but many people are still not enrolling in it. People say that it still costs too much money. They need all of their money to pay for things like food and rent . It would be great if everyone could have health insurance. People are working hard to come up with ways to make this happen. O...\n\nQ: Why is it very important for people to have health insurance?", "options": ["They can see a doctor free of charge.", "They can get special medical care.", "They can go to see a doctor as soon as possible.", "They can afford to see a doctor when they need to."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 486, "question": "Michael is the kind of guy you love to hate. He is always in a good mood and always has something positive to say. One day I went up to Michael and asked him, \"I don't get it. You can't be positive all the time. How do you do it?\" Michael replied, \"Each morning I wake up and say to myself 'Mike, you have two choices today. You can choose to be in a good mood or you can choose to be in a bad mood.' I choose to be in a good mood. Each time something bad happens, I can choose to be a victim or choose to learn from it. I choose to learn from it. Every time someone comes to me complaining I can choose to accept their complaining or I can point out the positive side of life. I choose the positive side of life.\" I often thought about that when I made a choice about life. Several years later, Mich...\n\nQ: From the passage we can infer that   _  .", "options": ["most people manage to lead a positive life at any time", "most people can't lead a positive life at any time", "only Michael can be so positive", "the author is always a sad person"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2832, "question": "It has been argued that an infant under three who is cared for outside the home may suffer because of the separation from his parents.The British psychoanalyst John Bowlby believes that separation from the parents during the sensitive \"attachment\" period from birth to three may scar a child's personality and incline to emotional problems in later life.Some people have drawn the conclusion from Bowlby's work that children should not be sent to day care before the age of three, and many people do believe this.But there are also arguments against such a strong conclusion. Firstly, anthropologists point out that the hidden love between children and parents found in modem societies does not usually exist in traditional societies.For example, we saw earlier that among the Ngonis the father and m...\n\nQ: The argument against Bowlby's conclusion shows that  _  .", "options": ["children have problems with day care", "there is no negative effect on infants who go to school before three", "there is a long-term effect on infants who go to school before three", "children who are sent to school before three are sent to mental illness"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2912, "question": "Most young people enjoy some forms of physical activities. It may be walking, cycling or swimming, or in winter, skating or skiing. It may be a game of some kind, football, hockey, golf, or tennis, it may be mountaineering. Those who have a passion for climbing high and difficult mountains are often looked upon with astonishment. Why are men and women willing to suffer cold and hardship, and to take risks on high mountaineering? This astonishment is caused probably by the difference between mountaineering and other forms of activity to which men give their leisure. Mountaineering is a sport and not a game. There are no manmade rules, as there are for such game as golf and football. There are, of course, rules of a different kind, which would be dangerous to ignore, but it is this freedom f...\n\nQ: Mountaineering is a sport which involves all the following things EXCEPT   _  .", "options": ["hardship", "comfort", "physical risk", "cold"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2403, "question": "Another of President Bush's critics on climate change and his former rival for the White House, Al Gore, is inprefix = st1 /Londonon Friday to launch an environmental project with the head of the Virgin Business Company, Richard Branson. They're announcing a multi-million dollar international prize to encourage development and research into new forms of low carbon technology. The prize will be available to anyone who can apply a successful method of removing large amounts of carbon dioxide from the atmosphere. Almost all scientists agree that we are experiencing global warming due to increased amounts of carbon dioxide in the atmosphere. Carbon dioxide is released when fuel is burned. Oil, coal and wood are all fuels that release the gas. When biological wasted breaks down, it also release...\n\nQ: Which of the following sentences is correct according to the text?", "options": ["Al Gore doesn't agree with President Bush's Policy on climate.", "Only a group or an organization will receive the prize.", "The prize will be given to anyone who can do research into low carbon technology", "Al Gore would like to help President Bush to solve the problem."], "answer": 0}, {"id": 3246, "question": "Italy is one country where beauty is prized more than any other virtue. That is, except in the small town of Piobbico, the self-declared World Capital of Ugly People. The road sign at the edge of the town even warns visitors that they are entering the ugly zone. People who consider themselves ugly have been gathering in Piobbico since the 1960s. That's when Ugly Club president Telesforo Lacobelli established a dating agency for women who believed they were too ugly to attract husbands. Lacobelli believes that he is ugly himself because he has a short nose in a country where long or large noses have always been considered beautiful. People from around the world travel to Piobbico to tell their sad stories of ugliness. During the annual Festival of the Ugly, which occurs on the first Sunday ...\n\nQ: Why is Lacobelli elected the president of the Ugly Club every year?", "options": ["Because he is the ugliest person in the whole world.", "Because his ugliness is always graded as bearable.", "Because he is a spokesperson for ugly people everywhere.", "Because he has won the members' trust and admiration."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1260, "question": "A new collection of photos brings an unsuccessful Antarctic voyage back to life. Frank Hurley's pictures would be outstanding----undoubtedly first-rate photo-journalism---if they had been made last week. In fact, they were shot from 1914 through 1916, most of them after a disastrous shipwreck , by a cameraman who had no reasonable expectation of survival. Many of the images were stored in an ice chest, under freezing water, in the damaged wooden ship. The ship was the Endurance, a small, tight, Norwegian-built three-master that was intended to take Sir Ernest Shackleton and a small crew of seamen and scientists, 27 men in all, to the southernmost shore of Antarctica's Weddell Sea. From that point Shackleton wanted to force a passage by dog sled across the continent. The journey was intende...\n\nQ: Who reached the South Pole first according to the text?", "options": ["Frank Hurley", "Ernest Shackleton", "Robert Falcon Scott", "Caroline Alexander"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 427, "question": "Aqeela Asifi, who fled to Pakistan as a young woman, has spent her life teaching other Afghan refugees. For her efforts, Ms. Asifi, who is 49, has won the 2015 UNHCR Nansen Refugee Award. She also gets $100,000 to help pay for her education projects. The UNHCR Nansen Refugee Award honors extraordinary service to people who have been forced from their homes. Eleanor Roosevelt, Graca Machel and Luciano Pavarotti are some of the other winners of the award. Asifi faced many problems in Afghanistan before she fled to Pakistan. Resources were limited and education for women was discouraged. However, in Pakistan, the 49-year-old was able to bring change to her conservative Afghan community. She persuaded parents to send their daughters to school in a tent at the Kot Chandana refugee village. The ...\n\nQ: According to the passage, Asifi was able to win the 2015 UNHCR Nansen Refugee award mainly because  _  .", "options": ["she suffered a lot more than other refugees who fled to Pakistan", "she was the kindest person all over the world", "she witnessed the cruelest event when she was in Afghanistan", "she made great contributions to refugees despite leaving her homeland"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 98, "question": "I've done many things that would make any parent proud. I've taken part in sports, community work and school events, but I am most proud to be a good big brother. I have to watch over four sisters and a brother, plus myself. That's quitea task, but one I feel I have gotten good at. My brother needs more attention than most siblings. When he was nine, he was hit by a pick-up truck on the way to the bus stop and lost use of the lower two-thirds of his body. He's been in a wheelchair for six years. My brother does many things, but sometimes he tries to do things he used to do but can't now. I' m always there with words of encouragement. I now watch my brother struggle to do as many things as he can within and beyond his limits. Should he fall, I will be the person to pick him up. I also watch...\n\nQ: How many people are probably there in the author's family?   _  .", "options": ["5", "6", "7", "8"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 424, "question": "Do you love holidays but hate gaining weight? You are not alone. Holidays are times for celebrating. Many people are worried about their weight. With proper planning, though, it is possible to keep normal weight during the holidays. The idea is to enjoy the holidays but not to eat too much. You don't have to turn away from the foods that you enjoy. Here are some tips for preventing weight gain and maintaining physical fitness: Don't skip meals. Before you leave home, have a small, low-fat meal or snack . This may help to avoid getting too excited before delicious foods. Control the amount of food. Use a small plate that may encourage you to \"load up \". You should be most comfortable eating an amount of food about the size of your fist . Begin with soup and fruit or vegetables. Fill up befo...\n\nQ: If the passage appeared in a newspaper, which section is the most suitable one?", "options": ["Holidays and Festivals section", "Health and Fitness section", "Fashion section", "Student Times Club section"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 485, "question": "Michael is the kind of guy you love to hate. He is always in a good mood and always has something positive to say. One day I went up to Michael and asked him, \"I don't get it. You can't be positive all the time. How do you do it?\" Michael replied, \"Each morning I wake up and say to myself 'Mike, you have two choices today. You can choose to be in a good mood or you can choose to be in a bad mood.' I choose to be in a good mood. Each time something bad happens, I can choose to be a victim or choose to learn from it. I choose to learn from it. Every time someone comes to me complaining I can choose to accept their complaining or I can point out the positive side of life. I choose the positive side of life.\" I often thought about that when I made a choice about life. Several years later, Mich...\n\nQ: Each time something bad happens, Michael chooses to   _  .", "options": ["be in a good mood", "learn from it", "complain about it", "ignore the negative side of it"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 1263, "question": "Have you ever stood side by side with an elephant and touched its ear or its long nose? A marvelous opportunity is offered here for you to experience working with these giant animals. The daily highlight is the walk from the elephant orphanage down to the river to bathe the elephants. Imaging what an amazing fun it is to watch an entire herd splashing around and rolling in the river just feet in front of you! This opportunity is available through a programme designed for visitors and volunteers to work in the world-famous government-run elephant orphanage in Pinnawela, Sri Lanka. The orphanage is regarded as one of the largest centers of its kind in the world, with one of the most successful captive breeding programmes for Asian elephants. Pinnawela Orphanage is situated in the hills of ce...\n\nQ: The passage's goal is to_.", "options": ["describe the elephant orphanage in Pinnawela, Sri Lanka.", "attract more tourists to come for sightseeing", "get volunteers for Pinnawela Elephant Orphanage", "call on people to care for baby elephants"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 144, "question": "In 1947 a group of famous people from the art world headed by an Austrian conductor decided to hold an intemational festival of music,dance and theatre in Edinburgh. The idea was to reunite Europe after the Second World War. At the same time, the \"Fringe\" appeared as a challenge to the official festival.Eight theatre groups turned up uninvited in 1947,in the belief that everyone should have the right to perform,and they did so in a public house disused for years. Soon,groups of studentsfirstly from Edinburgh University, and later from the universities of Oxford and Cambridge,Durham and Birmingham were making the journey to the Scottish capital each summer to perform theatre by little-known writers of plays in small church halls to the people of Edinburgh. Today the \"Fringe\",once less recog...\n\nQ: We may learn from the text that Edinburgh Festival.", "options": ["has become a non-official event", "has gone beyond an art festival", "gives shows all year round", "keeps growing rapidly"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 430, "question": "Dear son, The day that you see me old and I am already not in good health, have patience and try to understand me. If I get dirty when eating, if I can not dress, have patience and remember the hours I spent teaching it to you. If, when I speak to you, I repeat the same things thousand and one times, do not interrupt me, listen to me. When you were small, I had to read to you thousand and one times the same story until you got to sleep. When I do not want to have a shower, neither shame me nor scold me. Remember when I had to chase you with thousand excuses I invented, in order that you wanted to breathe. When you see my knowing little about new technologies, give me the necessary time and do not look at me with your mocking smile. I taught you how to do so many things: to eat good, to dre...\n\nQ: What does the father mainly want to say to his son in short?", "options": ["\" Help me to understand my life.\"", "\" Teach you how to live and survive.\"", "\" Share you how I taught you.\"", "\" Help to end my way with your love and patience.\""], "answer": 3}, {"id": 186, "question": "There are a number of different ways to study a language, each of which has advantages and disadvantages. You may find a combination of these is a best choice for you. If you can find a course in the language you want to learn in your country, this is quite a good way to study. A variety of courses are usually available, including part-time and full-time courses. If you look around, you can probably find a course that suits your needs. The main advantage of such courses is that you'll have a teacher to provide you with instructions, support and with whom to practice your language. You will also be studying with others who are at more or less the same level and you can exchange ideas with them and help one another. One choice is to study a language in a country where it's spoken. There are ...\n\nQ: The online courses    _   .", "options": ["are all free of charge", "can't be found everywhere", "can be easily taken on the Internet", "are all supported by teachers"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 256, "question": "It should be very clear that we live in a most spectacular time. It's a time when information is of primary importance. It's a time when new information technologies are fundamentally transforming the world in every aspect. Among the changes, which have come upon modern society, the ones in education are probably the most obvious and influential. New information technologies are accelerating changes in education, at the same time presenting revolutionary tools with the potential to make education more efficient and more effective than ever. The application of new information technologies has remarkably promoted the process of education. Online learning is probably the best case in point. As is often the case with \"technology\", online learning may appear to be horrible; it can sound like al...\n\nQ: It can be inferred from the passage that  _  .", "options": ["not all the people are in favor of online learning", "it is not easy to combine online learning with classroom learning", "in the future all the courses will be available online", "in a sense our survival in the world depends on online learning"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3117, "question": "Chocolate soap is supposed to be good for the skin. But it's not so good for the tongue. Unfortunately for the US soldiers of World War II, the chocolate bars the army gave them tasted like they were intended for use in the bath. In the army's defense, it wasn't trying to win any cooking awards. In fact, it specifically ordered that its chocolate bars not be too delicious, so soldiers wouldn't eat them too quickly. These bars were created for survival, not taste. \"They were awful,\" John Otto, a former army captain in World War II said, \"They were big, thick things, and they weren't any good. I tried them, but I had to be awfully hungry after I tried them once.\" As unappealing as the chocolate bars were to some, others like them. Samuel Hinkle, the chemist who created the chocolate bars, po...\n\nQ: Which of the following is TRUE according to the passage?", "options": ["The US soldiers used the chocolate bars as bath soap.", "The US army produced more chocolate bars than necessary for its soldiers.", "The US soldiers did not have enough food during World War II.", "European people regretted eating chocolate bars from the US soldiers."], "answer": 1}, {"id": 613, "question": "Educating Girls Is a Real Lifesaver Clare Short knows it. Every developing economist knows it. The World Bank knows it. The education of girls is the surest way to reduce poverty. The reason is simple. All the evidence shows that taking girls out of the fields and homes, and putting them behind desks, raises economic productivity, lowers infant and maternal death rates, reduces birth rates, and improves environmental management. Why, then, are 90 million primary school-age girls around the world not in school? For the same reason that when Charles Dickens was writing David Copperfield 150 years ago girls were absent from the British education system: Men in power mostly prefer _ that way, or are not interested enough in changing the situation to commit energy and money to doing so. The cou...\n\nQ: How many more infants will survive when 100 girls stay in school for another year?", "options": ["5", "6", "8", "12"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2839, "question": "My challenge for you is this: to read a book for 15 minutes every single day for a month. Let me explain a bit, by telling you where the challenge came from. I have many things in common with my dad, like music taste and sense of humor, but sadly reading isn't one of them. I can happily spend a whole day with a book, but my dad can't read a book for longer than about 5 minutes. He reads emails, websites and papers for work, but not books. He's busy so I think sitting down to read for just 15 minutes a day is a good way to relax and to introduce him to reading. My dad is by no means the only person who avoids books. I know lots of people would rather relax on their computers or in front of the TV. Everyone is different and has their own interests, but I think there're lots of benefits to re...\n\nQ: The author gives the example of his father in the text to show   _  .", "options": ["his father is very busy", "reading is very important to us", "his father likes reading", "many people have no habit of reading"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 2177, "question": "The modern Olympic Games, founded in 1896, began as contests between individuals, rather than among nations, with the hope of promoting world peace through sportsmanship. In the beginning, the games were open only to amateurs. An amateur is a person whose involvement in an activity---from sports to science or the arts---is purely for pleasure. Amateurs, whatever their contributions to a field, expect to receive no form of compensation ; professionals, in contrast, perform their work in order to earn a living. From the perspective of many athletes, however, the Olympic playing field has been far from level. Restricting the Olympics to amateurs has precluded the participation of many who could not afford to be unpaid. Countries have always desired to send their best athletes, not their wealt...\n\nQ: The statement \"the Olympic playing field has been far from level\" means that  _  .", "options": ["the ground the athletes played on was in bad condition", "the poorer players were given some advantages", "the rules did not work the same way for everyone", "amateurs were inferior to the professionals in many ways"], "answer": 2}, {"id": 502, "question": "Now some women are spending a weekend at Mother's Camp . There, husbands and children are not allowed. Why would a woman want to take a vacation without her family? Some women say they need time to be alone. At Mother's Camp a woman has room to herself. She can sleep, read or watch TV, and no one will bother her. No children will ask,\"Mom, what's for dinner?\" No husband will say, \"Oh, dear, I can't find any clean socks.\"In fact almost 50% of women in the United States work outside the home. Many of them work full-time and then come home to a second job-taking care of their homes and families. These working women say one of their biggest problems is housework. In the United States, working wives do about 75% of the housework. Many of their husbands say they want to help. But then they burn ...\n\nQ: At Mother's Camp, women can't_.", "options": ["watch TV", "read newspapers", "swim in the lake", "bring their husbands and children"], "answer": 3}, {"id": 1611, "question": "November not only marks the publication of Toni Morrison's eagerly anticipated eighth novel, Love, but it is also the tenth anniversary of her Nobel Prize for Literature. Morrison is the first black woman to receive a Nobel, and so honored before her in literature are only two black men:Wole Soyinka, the Nigerian playwright, poet and novelist, in 1986; and Derek Walcott, the Caribbean-born poet, in 1992. But Morrison is also the first and only American-born Nobel prizewinner for literature since 1962, the year novelist John Steinbeck received the award. Like Song of Solomon, Love is a multigenerational story, revealing the personal and communal Legacy of an outstanding black family. As Morrison scholars will tell you, Love is the third volume of a literary master's trilogy investigating th...\n\nQ: What can we learn about John Steinbeck?", "options": ["He was a black writer.", "He was born in America.", "He received the Nobel Prize after Morrison", "He was the first American novelist to win a Nobel"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 2355, "question": "Driver Wanted Clean driving license . Must be of smart appearance. Age over 25. Apply to : Capes Taxi, 17 Palace Road, Royston. Air Hostesses for International Flights Wanted Applicants must be between 20 and 33 years old. Height: 1.6 m to 1.75 m. Education to GCSE standard. Two languages. Must be able to swim. Apply to: Recruitment office, Southern Airlines, Heathrow Airport West. HR 37 KK. Teachers Needed For private language school. Having college education. Teaching experience unnecessary. Apply to: The Director of Studies, Instant Languages Ltd. 279 Canal Street, Royston....\n\nQ: What prevents Mary, aged 25, becoming an air hostess?", "options": ["She once broke a traffic law and was fined", "She can't speak Japanese very well.", "She has never worked as an air hostess before.", "She doesn't feel like working long hours flying abroad."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 3151, "question": "Paul received an automobile from his brother as a Christmas present. On Christmas Eve when Paul came out of his office, a street boy was walking around the shiny new car, admiring it. \"Is this your car, Mister?\" he asked. Paul nodded. \"My brother gave it to me for Christmas.\" The boy was astonished. \"You mean your brother gave it to you and it didn't cost you anything? Boy, I wish....\" He hesitated. Of course Paul knew what he was going to wish for. He was going to wish he had a brother like that. But what the kid said made Paul quite surprised. \"I wish,\" the boy went on, \"that I could be a brother like that.\" Paul looked at the boy in astonishment, and then impulsively he added, \"Would you like to take a ride in my automobile?\" \"Oh, yes, I'd love that.\" After a short ride, the boy turned ...\n\nQ: Which of the following is FALSE according to the passage?  _  .", "options": ["The boy had a brother who was disabled.", "Paul's brother gave him a car at Christmas.", "Paul had thought the boy were wishing for a brother like his.", "The boy wanted to show his neighbors that he could ride in a big car."], "answer": 3}, {"id": 346, "question": "Taichi with English narration A veteran Taichi teacher, about 38, teaches the basic 24 movements, pushinghands and self-defense techniques, suitable for the beginners and intermediate level. Time:10:00-12:00 a.m., every Sunday morning Place: Bamboo Garden Hotel, No 24, Xiaoshiqiao Hutong, jiuprefix = st1 /Gulou Street, Northwestof Drum Tower in the downtown. Fee: 60 yuan each time Chinese ink & water painting class To learn the techniques of painting a bird, flower, or lady with brushes. The Chinese philosophy and culture will also be included Time: 7:00-9:00p.m. every Wednesday Place: Library Bar, first floor, Tower B of East Gate Plaza ,right behind the poly plaza at the East Second Ring Road. Fee: 60 yuan each week Big-bowl-tea Ten yuan (US$1.2) for a cup of Chinese tea and live perform...\n\nQ: If you are a sport lover you can go to   _  .", "options": ["Library Bar", "Bamboo Garden Hotel", "Lao she Tea-House", "Wansheng Theatre"], "answer": 1}, {"id": 170, "question": "Directions: Read the following passage. The passage is followed by several questions or unfinished statements. For each of them there are four choices marked A,B,C and D. Choose the one that fits best according to the information given in the passage. It may be open to discussion which city is the most beautiful in the world. But in terms of \" the most livable\", Melbourne has ranked top in a survey done by the Economist Intelligence Unit (EIU) in August. In fact, four cities Down Under are among the top ten most livable cities. The climate in Australia is warm and mild, particularly in major coastal cities. As a result, people spend much time outdoors. They go to the beach, to the countryside, or play sports outdoors in fields. Take Melbourne for example. The city features many open green ...\n\nQ: Which will be the best title for this passage?", "options": ["Australia --- famous for its cultural diversity", "Australia --- home to sports", "Australia --- the most livable place in the world", "Australia --- fantastic natural environment"], "answer": 2}]